https://dupuis.ca/privacy-policy/

PrivacyPolicy
Dupuis is committed to making your privacy a priority while using our website. Most of the time you will be browsing our website anonymously, however we want our users to be aware that we collect data about their use of our site, and some of our online services require the collection of some personal information. This information is held in the highest confidence with Dupuis.
The following online services will require personal information and occasionally financial information such as credit card numbers:
Request for brochure
Add to mailing list
E-mail newsletter
Request for estimate
Register to bid
Subscribe to catalogue
Your personal information consists of your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number(s). This personal information is securely stored in a database and accessed only by authorized Dupuis staff.
We will only use this personal information for the following purposes:
To pre-approve you for bidding and to place on-line absentee bids
To process payments for services requested or to facilitate a transaction that you initiate
To send you information about our company, we may send you e-mail notices based on your expressed interests and bidding history
To contact you directly when necessary.
To help identify you and to gather statistical information (does not include personal information) about the use of our website
Sensitive information such as credit card numbers will be transmitted over a secure (encrypted) connection to prevent this information from being disclosed. Credit card authorization and payment facilitation companies will receive only the information required to verify and authorize your credit card and to process payments. They are under strict obligation to keep your credit card information and transaction records private and secure.
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WILL NOT BE:
Sold, loaned or rented to other parties for any purpose.
Shared with third parties unless you provide your consent in advance.
Our site may contain links to other websites, however, Dupuis is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. If you are concerned about privacy on these sites, please refer to their privacy statements.
At any time, you may send an e-mail to info@dupuis.ca and request that your e-mail address be removed from our lists or opt-out of receiving future mailings. Each e-mail we send will have an ‘unsubscribe’ functionality at the bottom of the page. If you have any questions about your personal information, please contact Customer Service. If you have any comments, questions or concerns about your privacy and security on Dupuis.ca please contact us.
Buying
Selling
Contact
Auction Calendar
Auction Estimates
Estate Appraisals
Sale Results
Catalogue Orders
1200 Bay Street, 9th FloorToronto, OntarioM5R 2A5 Canada(+1) 416-968-75001-800-879-8975info@dupuis.ca
© 1996-2020 Dupuis Fine Jewellery Auctioneers | All rights reserved | Privacy Policy
